#### Contact

elsieus@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/elsiewhite-897052a (LinkedIn) www.orlandohealth.com/ (Company)

## Top Skills

Board Certified Nursing Healthcare

## Languages

**English** 

### Certifications

Oncology Certified Nurse (OCN)
Certified Medical-Surgical
Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

# Elsie White

MSN RN

Orlando, Florida

# Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse, MSN in Leadership and Management with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Certifications in both Oncology and Medical Surgical. RN at Orlando Health's Radiation Oncology department in a clinical practice role leading a team for the Radiation Oncologist's practice. Proven history of collaboration throughout the UF Health Cancer Center's and Orlando Health's Surgical and Oncology departments. Over 10 years with in-patient critical care; Preceptor, Relief Charge nurse, staff nurse. Skilled in Nursing Leadership, Nursing Education, Critical Care, Interfacility Transport, Post-Operative Recovery, Medical-Surgical, Procedural Support, Moderate Sedation, and IV medication administration. Focused on patient & family patient-centered care delivered with compassion and transparency. I am currently pursuing exciting new opportunities towards taking a leading role in creating a healthier state of well being not only for patients, but also for their families and the community.

# Experience

Orlando Health

RN, MSN, CMSRN, OCN @ UF Health Outpatient Cancer Clinics March 2018 - June 2020 (2 years 4 months)

Orlando, Florida Area

**HCA** 

BSN, CMSRN

October 2008 - May 2018 (9 years 8 months)

Medical -Oncology, Surgical, Ortho.

## Education

Western Governors University

MSN Leadership and Management, Registered Nurse · (2016 - 2020)

Valencia Community College
Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2009 - 2012)